A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 2, Series 3 FA461
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 2, Series 3
1918-2008
Rockefeller Archive Center
Commonwealth Fund.
FA461
28.6 Cubic Feet 65 document boxes.
65 document boxes.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Conditions Governing Access note
Records more than 10 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Biographical/Historical note
The Commonwealth Fund was established in 1918 with an endowment of $10 million from Mrs. Stephen V. Harkness for "benevolent, religious, educational and like purposes." The early grants supported a variety of programs while generally promoting welfare, especially child welfare. Several grants were made in the field of medical research, but the Board of Directors decided in 1920 that this field was already sufficiently supported by other philanthropic organizations.
Despite this decision, by the mid-1920s the chief interest of the Fund had become public health, including mental hygiene, community health, rural hospitals, medical research, and medical education. Other grant areas included war relief, educational and legal research, child welfare, and international medical fellowships.
File Plan note
Former Classification: IX; IV 4B 4
Related Materials
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund Board of Directors records include:
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director/President, SG 1, Series 31
Other Finding Aids note
Other available finding aids describing the Commonwealth Fund records include:
FA247 Commonwealth Fund Harkness House drawings
FA276 Commonwealth Fund records, Annual Reports, SG 1, Series 4
FA277 Commonwealth Fund records, Archives/Library, SG 1, Series 5
FA278 Commonwealth Fund records, Austrian Program, SG 1, Series 6
FA279 Commonwealth Fund records, Board of Directors, SG 1, Series 7
FA280 Commonwealth Fund records, Capital Grants, SG 1, Series 8
FA281 Commonwealth Fund records, Child Health Demonstrations, SG 1, Series 9
FA282 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Community Clinics, SG 1, Series 10
FA283 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Health Studies, SG 1, Series 11
FA284 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Public Health, SG 1, Series 12
FA285 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Publications, SG 1, Series 13
FA286 Commonwealth Fund records, Division of Rural Hospitals, SG 1, Series 14
FA287 Commonwealth Fund records, Educational Research, SG 1, Series 15
FA288 Commonwealth Fund records, English Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 16
FA289 Commonwealth Fund records, Finance Committee, SG 1, Series 17
FA290 Commonwealth Fund records, Grants, SG 1, Series 18
FA291 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Family, SG 1, Series 19
FA292 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, SG 1, Series 20
FA428 Commonwealth Fund records, Harkness Fellowships, Fellows Reports, SG 1, Series 20A
FA293 Commonwealth Fund records, Institute for Child Guidance, SG 1, Series 21
FA294 Commonwealth Fund records, Interface Program, SG 1, Series 22
FA295 Commonwealth Fund records, Legal Research Program, SG 1, Series 23
FA296 Commonwealth Fund records, Living at Home Program, SG 1, Series 24
FA297 Commonwealth Fund records, Mental Hygiene Program, SG 1, Series 25
FA298 Commonwealth Fund records, Miscellaneous - unprocessed
FA299 Commonwealth Fund records, Personnel - unprocessed
FA300 Commonwealth Fund records, Pilgrim Trust, SG 1, Series 28
FA301 Commonwealth Fund records, Program for the Prevention of Delinquency, SG 1, Series 29
FA302 Commonwealth Fund records, Reference Files, SG 1, Series 30
FA303 Commonwealth Fund records, Reports of the General Director/President, SG 1, Series 31
FA304 Commonwealth Fund records, Treasurer, SG 1, Series 32
FA305 Commonwealth Fund records, Turndown Lists, SG 1, Series 33 - unprocessed
FA306 Commonwealth Fund records, Vertical File (R. Fitz), SG 1, Series 34 - unprocessed
FA307 Commonwealth Fund records, Visual Materials, SG 1, Series 35
FA389 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Historical Files, SG 1, Series 1
FA390 Commonwealth Fund records, Administration - Officers Files, SG 1, Series 2
FA429 Commonwealth Fund records, President, Margaret E. Mahoney, SG 2, Series 1
FA430 Commonwealth Fund records, Book Program, SG 2, Series 2
Arrangement
Arranged in 4 subseries as follows:
1. Board Meeting Minutes. 2. Board Reports. 3. Executive Committee. 4. Finance Committee.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: meeting minutes and reports.
Medical research; Medical education; Legal research; Legal issues; Law; Hygiene; Education, Rural; Child welfare; Child psychology; Child mental health; New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Public health; Public welfare; United States; War relief; Medicine, Rural; Medicine -- Scholarships, fellowships, etc.; Mental health
- Board Meeting Minutes, 1
  - 1975, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 1991 Nov. 26 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 1993-1995 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Vol. 1, 1918 Oct. 23 - 1924 Dec. 9 (Box 2, Folder 6, Folder 7)
  - Vol. 2, 1924 Dec. 9 - 1935 Dec. 2 (Box 2, Folder 9, Folder 8)
  - Vol. 3, 1935 Dec. 17 1943 Sept. 14 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Vol. 4, 1943 Oct. 14 - 1950 July (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Vol. 5, 1950 Oct. 19 - 1957 May (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Vol. 6, 1957 Nov. 14 - 1966 Feb. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Vol. 7, 1966 May 12 - 1972 Nov. 9 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Vol. 8, 1973 Feb. 8 - 1974 Nov. 21 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Vol. 9, 1975 Feb. 13 - 1976 Feb. 12 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Vol. 10, 1976 May 13 - 1977 Nov. 1 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Vol. 11, 1978 Feb. 9 - 1979 Nov. 8 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Vol. 12, 1980 Feb. 14 - Nov. 13 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Vol. 13, 1981 Feb. 12 - Nov. 12 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Vol. 14, 1982 April - Nov. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Vol. 15, 1983 April - 1987 July (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 1, 1918 Oct. 18 - 1924 Dec. 9 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted from scholarly access - Preservation Concerns
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 6, 1957 Nov. - 1966 Feb. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 8, 1973 Feb. 8 - 1974 Nov. 21 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 9, 1975 Feb. 13 - 1976 Feb. 12 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 10, 1976 May 13 - 1977 Nov. 1 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 11, 1978 Feb. 8 - 1979 Nov. 8 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 12, 1980 Feb. 14 - Nov. 13 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 13, 1981 Feb. 12 - Nov. 13 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 14, 1982 April - Nov. (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 15, 1983 April - 1987 July (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Bound Volumes - Vol. 16, 1987 July (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Board Reports/Board Books, 2
  - 1995 April 4 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1995 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 35, Folder 36)
  - Completed Grant Report, 1995 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Reports, 1995 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Models of Program Administration, 1995 July 13 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Retreat - Pocantico, 1995 July 13-15 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Retreat - Minutes, 1995 July 13-15 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Retreat - Tape Copies 1-10, 1995 July 13 (Box 11, Folder 42)
    Separated Materials
    Special Formats (audio, film, video, digital media, library materials, memorabilia, oversize, and photographic material) have been separated from the file. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
    - Retreat - Tape Copies 1-10, 1995 July 13; 2014:FA461:001; Digital Media
  - Selected Press Clippings, 1995 April-July (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Selected Press Clippings, 1995 July-Nov. (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1995 Nov. 14 (Box 12, Folder 46, Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Completed Grant Reports, 1995 Nov. 14 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Reports, 1995 Nov. 14 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Minutes, 1995 Nov. 14 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Quality of Life in New York City - Program Review, 1995 Nov. 14 (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Selected Press Clippings, 1995 Nov. - 1996 April (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1996 April 9 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Completed Grants Report, 1996 April 9 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1996 April 9 (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Minutes, 1996 April 9 (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Selected Press Clippings, 1996 April-June (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1996 July 12 (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1996 July 12 (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Minutes, 1996 July 12 (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Retreat, 1996 July 12-14 (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Retreat - Speeches and Seminars, 1996 July 12-14 (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1996 Nov. 12 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Completed Grants Report, 1996 Nov. 12 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1996 Nov. 12 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Minutes, 1996 Nov. 12 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1997 April 8 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Completed Grants Report, 1997 April 8 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1997 April 8 (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Minutes, 1997 April 8 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1997 July 10 (Box 14, Folder 70, Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1997 July 10 (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Minutes, 1997 July 10 (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Retreat - Briefing Material, 1997 July 10-11 (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box 15, Folder 75, Folder 76)
  - Completed Grants Report, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Minutes, 1997 Nov. 11 (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 1997 Nov. 24 (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1988 April 14 (Box 16, Folder 81, Folder 82)
  - Completed Grants Report, 1998 April 14 (Box 16, Folder 83)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1998 April 14 (Box 16, Folder 84)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1999 April 13 (Box 16, Folder 85)
  - Appendices, 1999 April 13 (Box 16, Folder 86)
  - Completed Grants Report, 1999 April 13 (Box 16, Folder 87)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1999 April 13 (Box 16, Folder 88)
  - Minutes, 1999 April 13 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1999 July 15 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Appendices, 1999 July 15 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1999 July 15 (Box 17, Folder 92)
  - Survey of Fund Audiences, 1999 July 15 (Box 17, Folder 93)
  - Site Visit - Briefing Material, 1999 July 14-16 (Box 17, Folder 94)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 1999 Nov. 9 (Box 17, Folder 95)
  - Appendices, 1999 Nov. 9 (Box 17, Folder 96)
  - Completed Grant Reports, 1999 Nov. 9 (Box 17, Folder 97)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 1999 Nov. 9 (Box 17, Folder 98)
  - Minutes, 1999 Nov. 9 (Box 18, Folder 99)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2000 April 11 (Box 18, Folder 100)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2000 April 11 (Box 18, Folder 102)
  - Minutes, 2000 April 11 (Box 18, Folder 103)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2000 July 12 (Box 18, Folder 104)
  - Finance Committee's ans Treasurer's Report, 2000 July 12 (Box 18, Folder 105)
  - Minutes, 2000 July 12 (Box 18, Folder 106)
  - Retreat, 2000 July 12-13 (Box 19, Folder 107)
  - Staff Retreat, 2000 July 24 (Box 19, Folder 108)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2000 Nov. 14 (Box 19, Folder 109)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2000 Nov. 14 (Box 19, Folder 110)
  - Minutes, 2000 Nov. 14 (Box 19, Folder 111)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2001 April 11 (Box 19, Folder 112)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2001 April 11 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2001 April 11 (Box 19, Folder 114)
  - Minutes, 2001 April 11 (Box 19, Folder 115)
  - Site Visit - Briefing Material, 2001 April 10-11 (Box 20, Folder 116)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2001 July 10 (Box 20, Folder 117)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2001 July 10 (Box 20, Folder 118)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2001 July 10 (Box 20, Folder 119)
  - Minutes, 2001 July 10 (Box 20, Folder 120)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2001 Nov. 13 (Box 20, Folder 121)
  - Finance Comittee's and Treasurer's Report, 2001 Nov. 13 (Box 20, Folder 122)
  - Minutes, 2001 Nov. 13 (Box 20, Folder 123)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 2002 Feb. 22 (Box 21, Folder 124)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2002 April 9 (Box 21, Folder 125)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2002 April 9 (Box 21, Folder 126)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2002 April 9 (Box 21, Folder 127)
  - Minutes, 2002 April 9 (Box 21, Folder 128)
  - Site Visit - Briefing Material, 2002 April 9 (Box 21, Folder 129)
  - Finance Committee Meeting, 2002 July 8 (Box 21, Folder 130)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2002 July 9 (Box 21, Folder 131)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2002 July 9 (Box 22, Folder 132)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2002 July 9 (Box 22, Folder 133)
  - Minutes, 2002 July 9 (Box 22, Folder 134)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2002 Nov. 12 (Box 22, Folder 135)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2002 Nov. 12 (Box 22, Folder 136)
  - Minutes, 2002 Nov. 12 (Box 22, Folder 137)
  - The Value - Added Foundation - The Role of Staff and Grantees' Views, 2002 Nov. 12 (Box 22, Folder 138)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2003 April 8 (Box 22, Folder 139)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2003 April 8 (Box 22, Folder 140)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2003 April 8 (Box 22, Folder 141)
  - Minutes, 2003 April 8 (Box 22, Folder 142)
  - Retreat - Briefing Material, 2003 April 8 (Box 23, Folder 143)
  - Report of the President & Staff (Box 23, Folder 144)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2003 July 8 (Box 23, Folder 145)
  - Minutes, 2003 July 8 (Box 23, Folder 146)
  - Report of the President & Staff (Box 23, Folder 147)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2003 Nov. 11 (Box 23, Folder 148)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2003 Nov. 11 (Box 23, Folder 149)
  - Minutes, 2003 Nov. 11 (Box 23, Folder 150)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2004 April 12 (Box 24, Folder 151)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2004 April 12 (Box 24, Folder 152)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2004 April 13 (Box 24, Folder 153)
  - Minutes, 2004 April 13 (Box 24, Folder 154)
  - Retreat - Briefing Material, 2004 April 12-13 (Box 24, Folder 155)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2004 July 13 (Box 24, Folder 156)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2004 July 13 (Box 24, Folder 157)
  - Finance Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2004 July 13 (Box 24, Folder 158)
  - Minutes, 2004 July 13 (Box 25, Folder 159)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2004 Nov. 9 (Box 25, Folder 160, Folder 161)
  - Investment Committee Meeting, 2004 Nov. 8 (Box 25, Folder 162)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2004 Nov. 9 (Box 25, Folder 163)
  - Making a Difference and Completed Grants Report, 2004 Nov. 9 (Box 25, Folder 164)
  - Minutes, 2004 Nov. 9 (Box 25, Folder 165)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2005 April 12 (Box 26, Folder 166)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2005 April 12 (Box 26, Folder 167)
  - Minutes, 2005 April 12 (Box 26, Folder 168)
  - Retreat - Briefing Material, 2005 April 11-12 (Box 26, Folder 169)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2005 July 12 (Box 26, Folder 170)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2005 July 12 (Box 26, Folder 171)
  - Minutes, 2005 July 12 (Box 26, Folder 172)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2005 Nov. 8 (Box 27, Folder 172A)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2005 Nov. 8 (Box 27, Folder 173)
  - Making a Difference and Completed Grants Report, 2005 Nov. 8 (Box 27, Folder 174)
  - Minutes, 2005 Nov. 8 (Box 27, Folder 175)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2006 April 11 (Box 27, Folder 176)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2006 April 11 (Box 27, Folder 177)
  - Minutes, 2006 April 11 (Box 27, Folder 178)
  - Retreat - Brirfing Materials, 2006 April 10-11 (Box 27, Folder 179)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2006 July 11 (Box 27, Folder 180)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2006 July 11 (Box 28, Folder 181)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2006 July 11 (Box 28, Folder 182)
  - Minutes, 2006 July 11 (Box 28, Folder 183)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2006 Nov. 14 (Box 28, Folder 184)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2006 Nov. 14 (Box 28, Folder 185)
  - Making a Difference and Completed Grants Report, 2006 Nov. 14 (Box 28, Folder 186)
  - Minutes, 2006 Nov. 13 (Box 28, Folder 187)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2007 April 10 (Box 28, Folder 188)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2007 Aptil 10 (Box 28, Folder 189)
  - Investment Committe's and Treasurer's Report, 2007 April 10 (Box 29, Folder 190)
  - Retreat - Briefing Materials, 2007 April 9-10 (Box 29, Folder 191)
  - Minutes, 2007 April 10 (Box 29, Folder 192)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2007 July 10 (Box 29, Folder 193)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2007 July 10 (Box 29, Folder 194)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2007 July 10 (Box 29, Folder 195)
  - Minutes, 2007 July 10 (Box 29, Folder 196)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2007 Nov. 13 (Box 29, Folder 197)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2007 Nov. 13 (Box 30, Folder 198)
  - Making a Difference and Completed Grants Report, 2007 Nov. 13 (Box 30, Folder 199)
  - Minutes, 2007 Nov. 13 (Box 30, Folder 200)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2008 April 15 (Box 30, Folder 201)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2008 April 15 (Box 30, Folder 202)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2008 April 15 (Box 30, Folder 203)
  - Minutes, 2008 April 15 (Box 30, Folder 204)
  - Retreat - Briefing Materials, 2008 April 14-15 (Box 30, Folder 205)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2008 July 15 (Box 31, Folder 206, Folder 207)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2008 July 15 (Box 31, Folder 208)
  - Investment Committee's and The Executive Vice President - COO/Treasurer, 2008 July 15 (Box 31, Folder 209)
  - Minutes, 2008 July 15 (Box 31, Folder 210)
  - Report of the President & Staff, 2008 Nov. 11 (Box 31, Folder 211)
  - Completed Grants Report, 2008 Nov. 11 (Box 31, Folder 212)
  - Investment Committee's and Treasurer's Report, 2008 Nov. 11 (Box 31, Folder 213)
  - Minutes, 2008 Nov. 11 (Box 31, Folder 214)
  - Board Book, 2009 April 13-14 (Box 66, Folder 392-393)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2020.
  - Board Book, 2009 July 14 (Box 66, Folder 394)
  - Board Book, 2009 November (Box 66, Folder 395-396)
  - Board Book, 2010 April 12-13 (Box 67, Folder 397)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2021.
  - Board Book, 2010 July (Box 67, Folder 398)
  - Board Book, 2010 November (Box 67, Folder 399)
  - Board Book, 2011 April (Box 68, Folder 400)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2022.
  - Board Book, 2011 July (Box 68, Folder 401)
  - Board Book, 2011 November (Box 68, Folder 402)
  - Book Board, 2012 April (Box 69, Folder 403)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2023.
  - Board Book, 2012 July (Box 69, Folder 404)
  - Board Book, 2012 November (Box 69, Folder 405)
  - Board Book, 2013 April 9 (Box 70, Folder 406)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2024.
  - Board Book, 2013 July 8-9 (Box 70, Folder 407)
  - Board Book, 2013 November 12 (Box 70, Folder 408)
  - Board Book, 2014 April 8 (Box 70, Folder 409)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2025.
  - Board Book, 2014 July 7-8 (Box 70, Folder 410)
  - Board Book, 2014 November (Box 71, Folder 411)
  - Board Book, 2015 April (Box 71, Folder 412)
    Restricted from scholarly access - Open in 2026.
  - Board Book, 2015 July (Box 71, Folder 413)
  - Program Plans 2007 (Box 72, Folder 414-416)
- Executive Committee, 3
  - Meetings, 1
    - 1920-1928 (Box 32, Folder 215)
    - 1929-1937 (Box 32, Folder 216)
    - 1938-1948 (Box 32, Folder 217)
    - 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 218)
    - 1949-1954 (Box 32, Folder 219)
    - 1950-1951 (Box 33, Folder 221, Folder 220)
    - 1952-1953 (Box 33, Folder 222, Folder 223)
    - 1954-1955 (Box 33, Folder 224)
    - 1957-1963 (Box 33, Folder 225)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 34, Folder 226)
    - 1966 (Box 34, Folder 227)
    - 1968 (Box 34, Folder 228, Folder 229)
    - 1965-1979 (Box 35, Folder 230)
    - 1967-1970 (Box 36, Folder 231, Folder 232)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 36, Folder 234, Folder 233)
    - 1971 Jan.-July (Box 37, Folder 236, Folder 235)
    - 1971 Sept.-Dec. (Box 37, Folder 237, Folder 238)
    - 1971-1972 April (Box 37, Folder 239, Box 38, Folder 240)
    - 1972 July-Dec. (Box 38, Folder 242, Folder 241)
    - 1973 Jan.-June (Box 38, Folder 244, Folder 243)
    - 1973 July-Dec. (Box 38, Folder 245, Box 39, Folder 246)
    - 1974 Jan.-June (Box 39, Folder 248, Folder 247)
    - 1974-1975 (Box 39, Folder 250, Folder 249)
    - 1973-1980 (Box 40, Folder 251)
    - 1975-1980 (Box 40, Folder 252, Folder 253)
- Finance Committee, 4
  - Agreements, 1919-1985 (Box 45, Folder 277)
  - Budget, 1
    - Balance Sheets, 1981 March 31 (Box 45, Folder 278)
    - Budget and Preparation, 1981 (Box 45, Folder 279)
  - Meetings, 2
    - 1979 June 30 (Box 45, Folder 280)
    - 1979 Nov. 2 (Box 45, Folder 281)
    - 1979 Dec. 31 (Box 45, Folder 282)
    - 1980 Feb. 5 (Box 45, Folder 283)
    - 1980 Feb. 14 (Box 46, Folder 284)
    - 1980 March 20 - April 19 (Box 46, Folder 285)
    - 1980 May 5 (Box 46, Folder 286)
    - 1980 May 8 (Box 46, Folder 287)
    - 1980 May 29 (Box 46, Folder 288)
    - 1980 July 21 (Box 46, Folder 289)
    - 1980 Sept. 25 (Box 46, Folder 290)
    - 1980 Nov. 3 (Box 46, Folder 291)
    - 1980 Nov. 13 (Box 46, Folder 292)
    - 1981 Feb. 2 (Box 47, Folder 293)
    - 1981 Feb. 12 (Box 47, Folder 294)
    - 1981 May (Box 47, Folder 295)
    - 1981 May 4 (Box 47, Folder 298, Folder 297, Folder 296)
    - 1981 May 13 (Box 47, Folder 299)
    - 1981 July 7 (Box 48, Folder 300)
    - 1981 July 29 (Box 48, Folder 303, Folder 301, Folder 302)
    - 1981 Sept. 22 (Box 48, Folder 304)
    - 1981 Oct. 28 (Box 48, Folder 305)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 48, Folder 306)
    - Resolutions Submitted, 1981 Nov. (Box 49, Folder 307)
    - 1981 Nov. 23 (Box 49, Folder 308)
    - 1982 Feb. 1-2, 4 (Box 49, Folder 309)
    - 1982 Feb. 9 (Box 49, Folder 310)
    - 1982 April 13 (Box 49, Folder 311)
    - Speaking Points - T. Ireland, III, 1982 April 13 (Box 49, Folder 312)
    - 1982 May 24, 26-27 (Box 49, Folder 313)